// Array of questions to be used in gameplay
let questions = [
    {
        question: 'Which book in the Bible mentions a huge man with six fingers on each hand and six toes on each foot?',
        choice1: '1. Genesis',
        choice2: '2. Samuel',
        choice3: '3. Exodus',
        choice4: '4. Revelation',
        answer: 2,
        verse: '"In still another battle, which took place at Gath, there was a huge man with six fingers on each hand and six toes on each foot-twenty-four in all. He also was descended from Rapha" - 2 Samuel 21:20 (NIV)',
    },

    {
        question: 'Whose dead bones brought a man back to life again after the body touched them?',
        choice1: '1. Eli',
        choice2: '2. Moses',
        choice3: '3. Joseph',
        choice4: '4. Elisha',
        answer: 4,
        verse: "Once while some Israelites were burying a man, suddenly they saw a band of raiders; so they threw the mans body into Elisha's tomb. When the body touched Elisha's bones, the man came to life and stood up on his feet. - 2 Kings 13:21 (NIV)",
    },

    {
        question: 'Which book in the Bible mentions a unicorn?',
        choice1: '1. Numbers',
        choice2: '2. Deuteronomy',
        choice3: '3. Job',
        choice4: '4. All of the above',
        answer: 4,
        verse: 'There are a few actually! Numbers 23:22, 24:8; Deuteronomy 33:17; Job 39:9-12; Psalm 22:21, 29:6, 92:10; Isaiah 34:7 (KJV)',
    },

    {
        question: 'How tall does the Bible say Goliath was?',
        choice1: '1. Over six feet tall',
        choice2: '2. Over nine feet tall',
        choice3: '3. 15 feet tall',
        choice4: '4. As tall as three horses stacked on top of each other',
        answer: 2,
        verse: "Then Goliath, a Philistine champion from Gath, came out of the Philistine ranks to face the forces of Israel. He was over nine feet tall! - 1 Samuel 17:4 (NLT)",
    },

    {
        question: 'What does the Bible say John the Baptist ate?',
        choice1: '1. Wafers and Milk',
        choice2: '2. Fish and Bread',
        choice3: '3. Figs and Wine',
        choice4: '4. Locusts and Wild Honey',
        answer: 4,
        verse: "John's clothes were made of camel's hair, and he had a leather belt around his waist. His food was locusts and wild honey. - Matthew 3:4 (NIV)",
    },

    {
        question: 'After Jesus fed 5000 people from just five loaves and two fishes, how many basketfuls of broken pieces did the disciples pick up?',
        choice1: '1. 12 Baskets',
        choice2: '2. 40 Baskets',
        choice3: '3. 70 Baskets',
        choice4: '4. There were no leftovers',
        answer: 1,
        verse: "They all ate and were satisfied, and the disciples picked up twelve basketfuls of broken pieces that were left over. - Matthew 14:20 (NIV)",
    },

    {
        question: 'Genesis 6:3 says: Then the Lord said, "My Spirit will not contend with humans forever, for they are mortal; their days will be ________." How many?',
        choice1: '1. 70 years',
        choice2: '2. 120 years',
        choice3: '3. 500 years',
        choice4: '4. Not very long',
        answer: 2,
        verse: 'Then the Lord said, "My Spirit will not contend with humans forever, for they are mortal; their days will be a hundred and twenty years." - Genesis 6:3 (NIV)',
    },

    {
        question: 'What does the Bible say manna tasted like?',
        choice1: '1. Wafers made with honey',
        choice2: '2. Locust and lentils',
        choice3: '3. Candy',
        choice4: '4. Broccoli',
        answer: 1,
        verse: '"The people of Israel called the bread manna. It was white like coriander seed and tasted like wafers made with honey. - Exodus 16:31 (NIV)"',
    },

    {
        question: "How old was Noah's father, Lamech, when he died?",
        choice1: '1. 77 years old',
        choice2: '2. 356 years old',
        choice3: '3. 777 years old',
        choice4: '4. He did not die',
        answer: 3,
        verse: '"Altogether, Lamech lived a total of 777 years, and then he died. - Genesis 5:31 (NIV)"',
    },

    {
        question: "What happened to Lot's wife when they were escaping the city's destruction and she turned to look back?",
        choice1: '1. She started showing up',
        choice2: '2. She became a pillar of salt',
        choice3: '3. She saw a ghost',
        choice4: '4. She stopped to build a snowman',
        answer: 2,
        verse: "But Lot's wife looked back, and she became a pillar of salt. - Genesis 19:26 (NIV)",
    },

    {
        question: "In Matthew's Gospel, how were the wise men warned not to go back to Herod after visiting Jesus?",
        choice1: '1. In a dream',
        choice2: '2. By an Angel',
        choice3: '3. They were led by the Spirit',
        choice4: '4. Jesus told them',
        answer: 2,
        verse: "And being warned in a dream not to return to Herod, they departed to their own country by another way. - Matthew 2:12 (ESV)",
    },

    {
        question: "According to Luke's Gospel, about how old was Jesus when he began his ministry?",
        choice1: '1. 21',
        choice2: '2. About 25',
        choice3: '3. About 30',
        choice4: '4. 30',
        answer: 3,
        verse: "Now Jesus himself was about thirty years old when he began his ministry. He was the son, so it was thought, of Joseph, the son of Heli. - Luke 3:23 (NIV)",
    },
];